<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-01-10T14:08:29-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">joey.io</title><subtitle>Coder Boi's Blog</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hit the Ground Running</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2019/01/10/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hit the Ground Running" /><published>2019-01-10T12:14:59-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-10T12:14:59-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2019/01/10/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2019/01/10/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;Like many software engineers and computer science students throughout their careers, they hit a rut. They begin to lose their passion for programming. I remember in my senior year of high school, I was so hungry to expand my knowledge in computer science beyond my only programming class AP Computer Science A. I took it upon myself to self study data structures and algorithms, a topic well beyond the high school curriculum. I would sacrifice my winter and spring breaks by going to the New York Public Library to keep on learning about this topic. With every new data structure I learned and implemented, it felt like I was leveling up in skill.
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/ds-100.png&quot; alt=&quot;ds-100&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
This decision to learn this topic eventually led to one of my greatest feats: a software engineering internship at Bloomberg L.P. The goal of this blog is to recapture that sort of excitement I used to have towards learning something new in this field which is why I will be documenting and discussing new things I’m learning whether it would be school work or independent studies. As a software engineer, I never want to stay stagnant. Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Like many software engineers and computer science students throughout their careers, they hit a rut. They begin to lose their passion for programming. I remember in my senior year of high school, I was so hungry to expand my knowledge in computer science beyond my only programming class AP Computer Science A. I took it upon myself to self study data structures and algorithms, a topic well beyond the high school curriculum. I would sacrifice my winter and spring breaks by going to the New York Public Library to keep on learning about this topic. With every new data structure I learned and implemented, it felt like I was leveling up in skill. This decision to learn this topic eventually led to one of my greatest feats: a software engineering internship at Bloomberg L.P. The goal of this blog is to recapture that sort of excitement I used to have towards learning something new in this field which is why I will be documenting and discussing new things I’m learning whether it would be school work or independent studies. As a software engineer, I never want to stay stagnant. Ever.</summary></entry></feed>